[
  {
    "question": "say",
    "answer": "said"
  },
  {
    "question": "make",
    "answer": "made"
  },
  {
    "question": "go",
    "answer": "went"
  },
  {
    "question": "take",
    "answer": "took"
  },
  {
    "question": "come",
    "answer": "came"
  },
  {
    "question": "see",
    "answer": "saw"
  },
  {
    "question": "know",
    "answer": "knew"
  },
  {
    "question": "get",
    "answer": "got"
  },
  {
    "question": "give",
    "answer": "gave"
  },
  {
    "question": "find",
    "answer": "found"
  },
  {
    "question": "think",
    "answer": "thought"
  },
  {
    "question": "tell",
    "answer": "told"
  },
  {
    "question": "become",
    "answer": "became"
  },
  {
    "question": "show",
    "answer": "showed"
  },
  {
    "question": "leave",
    "answer": "left"
  }
]